https://tabutoys.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This policy covers how we collect, use, disclose, store and protect your personal information. Please read this policy carefully before accessing or using our website.
By accessing or using this website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth herein.
Personal information collected
We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using the tabutoys.com. This information includes your name, email address and a password when you create your shopping Account. While you can browse our online store without opening an account, you will need to create an account in order to make purchases or create a wishlist.
We may also ask for personal information when you contact our Customer Service. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.
Cookies
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Children’s Privacy
Tabutoys.com contains sexually-oriented adult material that is not intended for individuals under 18 years of age. Tabutoys.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from individuals under 18 years of age who visit the Website. If a person under 18 years of age has provided us with personally identifiable information, we ask that a parent or guardian immediately contact us at 1-800-921-1266 for assistance.
Purchase Information
When you make a purchase using a credit card, we collect your name and billing address for the card, the card type, number, and expiration date. We collect this information in order to verify your billing address.
We also collect information that allows us to ship your purchase and keep you informed of the status of your order. This includes your email address and the name, address, and telephone number of the intended recipient(s). Billing information may also be provided over the phone by calling Tabutoys.com at 1-800-921-1266.
User Content
Tabutoys.com may post reviews, comments, letters, photographs and/or videos provided to us by our customers. When you submit the materials and other information to us you represent that you are authorized to submit such materials or other information and you grant to Tabutoys a non-exclusive, royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual license, with the right to sub-license, to reproduce, distribute, transmit, create derivative works of, publicly display and publicly perform any materials and other information (including, without limitation, ideas contained therein for new or improved products) you submit to any public areas of the Website (such as bulletin boards, forums and newsgroups), e-mail to Tabutoys.com or any other means and in any media now known or hereafter developed.
You also grant to Tabutoys.com the right to use your name in connection with the submitted materials and other information as well as in connection with all advertising, marketing and promotional material related thereto. You agree that you shall have no recourse against Tabutoys.com for any alleged or actual infringement or misappropriation of any proprietary right in your submitted materials and other information to the Website.
With whom we share your personal information
We never sell or rent your email address to unaffiliated companies. We also do not sell other personal customer information to unaffiliated third-parties. We will share personal customer information that we collect only with Tabutoys.com agents, representatives and trusted service providers for the limited purposes of fulfilling customer orders, communicating to customers; providing customer service, and completing credit card transactions.
Assumption of Risk
YOU ASSUME TOTAL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND THE INTERNET. TABUTOYS PROVIDES THE WEBSITE AND RELATED INFORMATION "AS IS" AND DOES NOT MAKE ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR ENDORSEMENTS WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR NONINFRINGEMENT, OR THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE) WITH REGARD TO THE SERVICE, ANY MERCHANDISE INFORMATION OR SERVICE PROVIDED THROUGH THE SERVICE OR ON THE INTERNET GENERALLY, AND TABUTOYS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY COST OR DAMAGE ARISING EITHER DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY FROM ANY SUCH TRANSACTION. IT IS SOLELY YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS AND USEFULNESS OF ALL OPINIONS, ADVICE, SERVICES, MERCHANDISE AND OTHER INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THE SERVICE OR ON THE INTERNET GENERALLY. TABUTOYS DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE OR THAT DEFECTS IN THE SERVICE WILL BE CORRECTED.
YOU UNDERSTAND FURTHER THAT THE PURE NATURE OF THE INTERNET CONTAINS UNEDITED MATERIALS SOME OF WHICH ARE SEXUALLY EXPLICIT OR MAY BE OFFENSIVE TO YOU. YOUR ACCESS TO SUCH MATERIALS IS AT YOUR RISK. TABUTOYS HAS NO CONTROL OVER AND ACCEPTS NO RESPONSIBILITY WHATSOEVER FOR SUCH MATERIALS.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT WILL TABUTOYS BE LIABLE FOR (I) ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR INFORMATION, AND THE LIKE) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICE, OR ANY INFORMATION, OR TRANSACTIONS PROVIDED ON THE SERVICE OR WEBSITE, OR DOWNLOADED FROM THE SERVICE OR WEBSITE, OR ANY DELAY OF SUCH INFORMATION OR SERVICE OR WEBSITE. EVEN IF TABUTOYS OR ITS AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR (II) ANY CLAIM ATTRIBUTABLE TO ERRORS, OMISSIONS, OR OTHER INACCURACIES IN THE SERVICE, WEBSITE AND/OR MATERIALS OR INFORMATION DOWNLOADED THROUGH THE SERVICE OR WEBSITE. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, TABUTOYS’S LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Tabutoys.com, its affiliates, officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, vendors and any third party information providers from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees, resulting from any violation of this Agreement (including negligent or wrongful conduct) by you or any other person accessing the Website.
Third Party Rights
The Legal Notices are for the benefit of Tabutoys.com and its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, suppliers, and any third party information providers to the Website. Each of these individuals or entities shall have the right to assert and enforce those provisions directly against you on its own behalf.
OK
